Monica.
Hey, can I borrow the Porsche?
Okay.
All right!
But, uh...
what is it not?
A place to entertain
my lady friends.
And what else is it not?
A place to eat spaghetti.
Very good.
Thanks.
What do you need it for anyway?
Oh, the Powerball Lottery
is up to $300 million
and they don't sell tickets
here in New York, so...
Oh, so you're driving
up to Connecticut?
Yeah, Connecticut,
not... West Virginia.
Hey, maybe I'll
drive you up there.
I'd like to buy
some tickets myself.
Yeah, with Chandler
not getting paid,
we could really use
$300 million.
Yes, because if I was
at my old job,
we'd say, "$300 million?
No, thank you."
Hey, will you get me
tickets, too?
Yeah, me, too.
Sure.
Ooh! I have an idea.
Why don't we all
pitch in 50 bucks,
we'll pool our money together,
and then if we win,
we'll split it.
( all agreeing )
That's a great idea.
No, thanks.
You don't want
to win the lottery?
Uh, sure I do.
I also want to be king
of my own country
and find out what happened
to Amelia Earhart.
Still on
Amelia Earhart?
The woman just vanished.
Seriously, Ross,
you don't want in on this?
No. Do you know what your odds
are of winning the lottery?
I mean, you have a better chance
of being struck
by lightning 42 times.
Yes, but there's
six of us,
so we'd only have
to get struck
by lightning
seven times.
I like those odds.
Seriously, you guys,
I can't believe
you're going to spend
$250 on the lottery.
I mean, that's such
a bunch of boohockey.
I'll ask.
Boohockey?
Oh, oh, we think Emma's
about to start talking
so we're trying to be careful
about what words
we use in front of her.
Yeah, so get ready to hear a lot
of "boohockey," "gosh darn it"
and "brother pucker."
How do you know she's
going to start talking?
Well, when I talk to her,
I almost feel
like she understands
what I'm saying.
Kinda like Joey.
What's that now?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ When the rain starts to pour ♪
♪ I'll be there for you ♪
♪ Like I've been there before ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
God, look at all
these tickets.
It's so exciting.
I haven't won anything
since the sixth grade.
Pie-eating contest?
Oh, you assume
because I was heavy
that's the only way
I could win something?
No, I saw a picture of you
covered in blueberries.
That was a good day.
They're towing your car!
They're towing
your car!
I parked in a garage on Morton.
They're towing a car
and I am...
seeing spots.
Oh, my God, Ross,
you don't have Emma.
And Rachel, you
don't have Emma.
Where is Emma?
Who has Emma?!
Joey, relax. My mother
picked her up two hours ago.
You were there.
I was?
Yes, and you talked to her.
I did?
She dropped off a casserole.
Oh, yeah, the
casserole lady.
So, did you come by
to watch us win
the big bucks?
Yeah, and then
I figured, after you win,
we can all go out to the balcony
and see a night rainbow
with gremlins dancing
on top of it.
( telephone ringing )
Don't touch the phone!
I'll get it,
I'll get it!
Hello.
You think he washed
his hands?
Hey, Charlie, what do you know?
What's going on?
Chandler's supposed to find out
if he's getting an assistant job
at his ad agency
but out of 15 interns,
they're only hiring three.
Ooh, tough odds.
Yeah, if only
it were a sure thing
like your 24-state lottery.
Yeah, look who's coming around.
Damn it. All right,
call me when you know more.
JOEY:
Did you get it?
One of the slots got filled.
By you?
Sense the tone.
No, that kid Nate got it.
Oh, I hate that guy.
Come on, kid,
pull up your pants!
I know.
Well, there's
two spots left, right?
Yeah. I mean,
I want this so much.
I mean,
I want to get one,
I want my friend Charlie
to get one...
Except I don't care
about Charlie.
Hey, you guys!
ALL:
Hey!
Okay, you are not
going to believe this.
I just saw my psychic
and she said I was definitely
going to win
the lottery tonight.
Hey, that reminds me.
I thought we could use
some extra luck,
so I brought a wishbone
home from work.
A psychic and a wishbone?
Guys, give someone
else a chance.
All right, who
wants to do it?
Oh, can I?
Vegetarians never get
to do the wishbone.
It's really not fair either,
because, you know, just
because we don't eat the meat
doesn't mean we don't like
to play with the carcasses.
All right. Hey, Rach?
No, I'm good--
I don't want to get
that turkey smell
all over my hands.
I'll do it!
Got to get the casserole stink
off of mine.
Okay.
I hope I win.
Well, it doesn't really matter.
You're both wishing
for the same thing, right?
I can't tell you what I'm
wishing for, or else, you know,
it won't come true.
Right, but we know
what you're wishing for.
I can't really say.
I understand,
but you're wishing
for what we think you're
wishing for, aren't you?
I'm not really comfortable
with these questions.
Please!
Just do it.
Okay, ready: one, two...
three!
I won. Hey!
You know what?
I'm sure your wish
is gonna come true,
but, you guys, just in case,
maybe a genie will come out
if we rub this lamp... Ow!
That thing gets hot!
You know, Ross, just
keep making your jokes.
How are you
going to feel
if we actually do win?
Uh, you're not gonna win.
Oh, I know, I know,
the odds are against us,
but somebody has to win,
and it could be us
and then how you gonna feel?
You know, we're gonna be all
like, "Oh, everybody
let's take our helicopters
up to the Cape,"
and you're gonna,
and you're gonna be all like,
"Oh, I can't, guys,
I'll have to meet you up there.
I gotta gas up the Hyundai."
Okay, I've heard myself on tape
and I sound nothing like that.
I can see the headline now.
"Lottery Winners' Friend,
Filled With Regret,
Eats Own Arm."
Why would I
eat my own arm?
You wouldn't,
but we own the paper.
We can print whatever we want.
You know what, Ross?
I'm going to throw in
50 bucks for you.
Why?
Because I know
that you think
that the lottery
is boohockey...
but we're all here
and we're gonna
watch the numbers
and have fun.
And you're my brother
and I want you to
be a part of this.
You don't have to do that.
I mean, I'll pay for myself,
but just the fact that
you want me to have
fun with you guys,
that's so sweet.
Come here.
Get a room.
Okay, so, now that you're in,
what are you gonna do if we win?
I don't know.
I'll probably just invest it.
Ooh, calm down.
Seriously,
that's your fantasy?
To invest it?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I say invest it?
I meant
be cool and piss it all away.
Ooh! Ooh! I know.
We should pool
all our money
and buy the Knicks.
I don't really care
about the Knicks.
Oh, you will when I pick you
as starting forward.
You would do that?
I never get picked.
You know, I'm not
sure a sports team
is the way to go.
You're not going
to let me buy the Knicks?
I can't believe you're taking
this away from me.
You're right, it has been
your dream for over 15 seconds.
Uh, how long until they
announce the numbers, Mommy?
I'll take this one, too.
Uh... "Mommy"?
Oh, I've gotten into the habit
of calling Rachel "Mommy"
when we're around Emma,
which, I now realize,
we are not.
I'm hoping that if
she hears it enough,
it'll be her
first word.
Although, if we're
going to do that,
we should probably
call me Daddy, too.
Ooh. I like that, Daddy.
I, uh... I was just
talking about Rachel.
Ooh, is Daddy getting angry?
Is Daddy going to spank me?
Well, that depends.
Have you been a bad g...
No, I can't. I can't.
( telephone ringing )
Hello. Hello.
Hey, Charlie, did
anybody else hear?
What? Susan got it?
How?
Oh, man, I would
have slept with him.
All right. Bye.
Dude, I'm sorry,
but, hey, there's
one spot left, right?
Well, Charlie's
gonna get that.
Hey, don't say that.
You got just as
good a chance
as anybody else of
getting that job.
He is the boss's son.
Come on, lottery!
Yeah! Yeah!
Oop! Ooh, you guys,
it starts in, like,
20 minutes.
Okay, all right,
here we go.
So, we need to sort
through the tickets
as quickly as possible
to see if we've won.
So does anybody have
any ideas how to organize this?
Okay, how about this?
We divide them
into six groups of 40
and the remaining ten
can be read
by whoever finishes
their pile first.
Oh, I have another idea.
I'm sorry-- idea time is over.
Okay, well,
are all the tickets
in the bowl?
Yeah.
What about the ones
you have on the nightstand?
There are no tickets
on the nightstand.
Yes, there are.
I just saw them
a few minutes ago.
Uh, no, you didn't.
You must be mistaken.
Honey, there are
like 20 tickets
on the nightstand.
Chandler, sense the tone.
Well, well, well.
Look what Mommy found.
Okay, fine.
I bought 20 extra tickets
for me and Chandler.
( gasps )
The psychic also said
that I would be betrayed.
I can't believe this.
I thought we were all
in this together.
Hey, you just got in
five minutes ago.
Three minutes ago.
I don't know
why that's important.
Oh, look, hey,
I was with you
the whole time we
were in Connecticut.
When did you
even get those?
When you were reading
the dirty magazines
without taking off the plastic.
I'll show you how.
Okay, well, Monica, suppose one
of your special tickets wins.
How are you going to feel
when you win the lottery
and you lose all your friends?
Please, if I win the lottery,
you guys are not gonna leave me.
Someone gave me a basket
of mini-muffins last week
and I couldn't get rid
of you for three days.
Chandler, would
you just tell her
what she did
was wrong?
She's right. You shouldn't
have bought tickets
just for us.
Let me finish.
However...
it doesn't look like
I'm gonna get this job
so I can't afford
to have principles.
So screw you!
The tickets are ours!
( gasps )
There's the man I married.
All right. Believe me,
if you win the lottery
it's the last you're
gonna hear from us.
Fine. Don't be my friends.
I'll buy new friends.
Yeah, and then I'll pay
for their plastic surgery
so they'd look
just like you.
All right, you know what?
That's it.
I want my share
of the tickets.
Yeah, I want
my tickets, too--
and I'm buying the Knicks...
and Steffi Graf!
( chortles )
Hold it-- then I want
mine, too, and if I win,
I'm going to put it all
into a very low-yield bond.
No! You guys,
we got to keep
all the tickets together.
MONICA:
No, no!
We should divide them up,
and I should get extra
because we used
my car to buy them!
Hey! Hey! If anybody gets
extra tickets, it should be me!
This whole thing
was my idea!
Oh, yeah, thanks
for inventing the lottery.
RACHEL:
That's it.
Just give them to me
and I'll split them up.
Ow!
( shrieks )
Hey, hey.
I can't take it anymore!
I'm putting an end to this!
Okay, if she jumps,
I get her tickets.
Wait! No, no!
Hey, hey!
If we're not
doing this together,
we're not doing it at all.
Say good-bye
to your tickets.
No! No! No!
Do not come any closer!
Can I come a
little bit closer?
Valuable things are
getting squished.
Now, what's more important?
Your friends, or money?
Friends!
Money!
Friends.
And, Monica, what about
your extra tickets?
They're all in there.
Even these five
that I hid in my bra.
Monica!
Okay. Good.
You guys were so scared.
There was no way I was
gonna dump this thing...
( shrieks )
God! No!
I think I broke your bowl.
Go! Go! Go!
Go! Go!
What a beautiful night
to be running around the street
looking for tickets.
And the wind sure made it fun.
Phoebe, we lost
half of them.
So what? Monica,
we have the winning ticket.
My psychic said I was going
to win, remember?
Weird your psychic
didn't mention anything
about the scary pigeon.
As a matter of fact, she said
that's how I'm going to die.
So excuse me for being
a little skittish.
Hey, there's two messages.
This could be from work.
Play them.
Okay.
Here we go.
( beep )
PHOEBE:
Hello? This is the pigeon
from the balcony
calling to apologize.
I shouldn't have
knocked the tickets
out of the pretty lady's hand.
It was all my fault--
not hers.
Bye. Coo.
Well, I bet that was
very hard for him to do.
( beep )
Hey, Chandler, it's Charlie.
This is it. Shh!
Listen, um, it turns out
I got the last spot.
I'm really sorry, man.
It was a lot of fun
working with you.
Give me a call if you want.
Gosh, I'm so sorry, honey.
Sorry about that, man.
That is so unfair.
It's like that time they
promoted Sandra over me at work.
Oh, was she related
to Ralph Lauren?
No, she was just much better
at her job than me.
Guys, the drawing's
about to start.
We should call my mom's house
and say good night to Emma
before she goes down.
Oh, yeah, it's a good idea.
Honey, you're being
very strong about this.
I know how badly
you wanted that job.
Yeah, you know, I really
thought I deserved it.
But let's go win
the lottery.
I mean, we still have
130 chances to win, right?
131.
Good night, sweetheart.
I love you.
And remember, you're
Daddy's little girl.
Phoebe's totally
ruined that for me.
Hi, Mom.
Oh, put her back on.
( TV plays )
Rach, come on, they're
announcing the numbers.
My God, I can already
feel myself changing.
Here are your official
Powerball numbers.
We have 53.
I've got that.
Ooh, ooh, ooh,
we have one, too.
We are on the road, people.
Check those tickets carefully.
Come on!
Mom, please.
I know you love your new lips.
But I can barely understand you.
Would you please just let me
say good night to my daughter?
...and here we go,
the Powerball is seven.
All right, check your numbers!
Make me rich.
Have a safe, happy holiday.
Good night.
Oh, guys, you're not going
to believe this.
I was just saying
good night to Emma
and she said
her first words.
What?
Really?
What did she say?
She said "gleba."
Make me rich!
Isn't that amazing?
Yeah, no, no, no.
That's great.
Why aren't you
more excited?
Uh, Rach, "gleba" is not a word.
Well, of course it is.
Okay, what does it mean?
Well, I don't know
all the words.
You know, I'm just glad I didn't
miss my daughter's first word.
Well, yes, you did.
"Gleba" is a word.
Okay, use it in a sentence.
Okay.
Uh, "Emma just said gleba."
It's not a word.
Okay, okay, okay, fine.
I'm going to look it up.
Oh, oh, okay, great.
You know what,
while you're at it,
she said another word
the other day.
Why don't you look up...
( sputters )
All right, okay, okay, gleba.
Gleba, gleba... gleba!
Ah, here it is.
"The fleshy, spore-bearing
inner mass of a certain fungi."
She's going to be
a scientist.
Damn it.
Anybody got
anything?
No.
I'm still
looking through mine.
Just double checking.
No. No. No.
No!
( telephone rings )
Hello?
Hold on.
It's your boss.
Ah, the I'm-sorry-
I-rejected-you phone call.
Not used to getting
these from guys.
Hey, Steve.
Chandler, hi.
I'm sure you've heard
we filled the three positions.
We just felt that with
your maturity and experience,
you wouldn't be happy
being someone's assistant.
Well, no, no, I'd love to be
somebody's assistant.
Answering phones, getting
coffee, I live for that stuff.
And I'm not too mature.
Farts, boobies, butt cracks.
Chandler, you were the strongest
person in the program.
We're offering you the position
of junior copywriter.
Me? The guy who just said
"butt cracks"?
Yes, that's right.
We're excited about
the level of sophistication
you'll be bringing to the job.
Okay, well, thanks.
You won't regret it.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What?
Oh, yeah, I'm going to
be a junior copywriter.
Wow!
That's great!
Congratulations.
Sweetie,
I'm so proud of you.
Does that mean I get
the good loving tonight?
You bet.
No TV or anything.
Hey, that is so great
about the job.
Thanks, man.
And I'd like to
think I had a little
something to do with it.
Really, why?
Well, before,
with the wishbone...
I, uh... I didn't wish
we would win the lottery.
I wished you'd
get the job.
Oh, yeah?
Listen, don't tell Monica.
She'll rip your heart right out.
Oh, yeah.
Wow, you know what?
There was a little part of me
that really thought
we were going to win.
Me, too.
So much for my
dinosaur-slash-Amelia Earhart
theme park.
You guys...
what was the Powerball
number again?
Seven.
We won.
What?
We won!
What?!
Let me see!
Don't tear it.
Phoebe, you don't have
any of the first five numbers.
I know that.
But look, we got
the Powerball number.
We won three dollars!
Wow, you think we should
get that over 20 years
or go for the big payout?
I don't care, I've never
won anything before.
I can't believe this!
So, Pheebs, what are
you going to do with
your three dollars?
Well, it's not all mine.
We all get 50 cents.
You know what,
you can have mine.
Me, too.
Well, I guess
if everybody else is.
Hey, guys.
I just called the
Powerball hotline.
Can you believe it?
Nobody won.
I beg to differ.
Maybe nobody
won the jackpot,
but there was this guy
in here earlier
and he found a ticket
on the street, right outside,
and won $10,000.
Coo. Again...
don't blame the pretty lady.
It was not her fault.
It was me, the pigeon. Coo.
Seriously,
stop staring at her.
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org